Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
-Hi. Sharon.
-Good morning.
Hi. neighbor.
I'm Sharon Norman.
and as head of the
Neighborhood Welcome Committee.
I welcome you
with this welcome walnut pie.
Wow.
I feel very welcomed.
No sugar. dairy or gluten.
So no flavor.
I'm kidding.
Oh. this is so thoughtful.
I'm Beryl.
Oh. I know all about you.
Beryl Nix.
Uh. or at least
what's public record.
So my reputation precedes me.
We like to know who's joining
our little hamlet here.
"We"?
We are a very close-knit
community.
and you lucked out living
next door to me.
I am the head
of the Garden Club.
the PTA. the Social Committee.
Social Committee?
So you know where
I can get the good drugs.
Kidding again. Sharon.
Oh. I could tell
you were gonna be fun.
Guilty as charged.
But I moved here
to get away from all the fun
of the city and its...
everything.
The quiet nothing of here
will help me focus on my art.
You'll find there's
a lot of life here.
This is our community calendar.
And while we do not have an HOA.
I put together a list
of suggested guidelines
that we like to follow.
Oh. can't wait
to meet this "we."
It's things like
outdoor light wattages.
noise considerations
like the wind chimes
that you put in
over the weekend on your yard.
They haven't broken any
noise ordinances... yet.
-Just kidding.
-You got me.
Oh. landscape maintenance.
You know. that big old wild tree
on our property line
blocks a lot of
the natural light to my studio.
Again. these are just
suggested guidelines.
This is our Towering Maple.
and it has been sort of
grandfathered in.
Is it?
We find that very convenient.
Anyway. thank you for the pie.
rules and hopefully drugs.
Just kidding. neighbor.
Do we have new blossoms?
Ugh. I am buying her shades.
Phil will open up his shop
early for me.
It's not a big deal.
I was looking at the painting.
It's not bad.
The '60s are dead. honey.
She's not even a real artist.
She's just rich and bored.
And cold. apparently.
I see more nudity
at work every day.
The sordid life
of an anesthesiologist.
Indeed.
Have a good day. please.
I always do.
Beryl is having a party again.
We're invited. Could be fun.
Ugh.
Hard pass.
And she's again asking us
to trim the tree.
"The Towering is overpowering."
Rad. Doughnuts.
Absolutely not.
No. this is bribery.
Put that back.
Take an apple. Go upstairs.
This is adult stuff.
Seems pretty childish to me.
The only thing worse
than wind chimes:
drum circles.
She's keeping me awake
on purpose.
Well. at least
she's on the beat.
Come back to bed.
It's so funny to you.
You're gone all day.
and I'm dealing with
this tension and harassment.
Honey. I'm in an operating room.
And how many years
have I come home to you
fired up about noise
or too many cars parked
on the street or the...
the arbor rights fight?
The maple is a bit unruly.
Do you remember
when we found this house?
We walked up that drive.
we saw that tree.
and we both knew
that we were gonna make
this house our home.
And under that unruly maple...
...we'd lie there
and you'd read to me
with my belly out to here.
That's where Avery took
her first steps.
That's where she tested
her bravery
and she climbed higher and
higher under our watchful gaze.
And when I see our...
Towering Maple on the horizon.
I know that I am almost home.
It grows. and it grows with us.
I didn't realize how important
that tree is to you.
It's family.
And no member
of our family will ever.
ever be touched by that woman.
Your tree is dead.
But how? What happened?
It's nature. man.
It sucks sometimes.
Oh. Sharon.
I'm so sorry.
It was such a massive presence
in all our lives.
And the final Halloween event
on the agenda is
the Haunted Maze.
And this year.
it goes to Beryl Nix.
I will email you the names
of the high school volunteers
who are going to help. and...
Well. Sharon.
we've been talking.
"We"?
The ladies and I
think this year
I should amp up the maze.
Make it really. really scary.
unlike past... no offense...
boring years.
No offense.
None taken.
But we don't want
to traumatize the kids.
Brayden had to sleep in bed
with you for a week
after last year's.
That's because he saw
a real spider in the maze.
I think Beryl has a great idea...
spice it up.
Okay.
What did you have in mind?
Oh. you know me.
I take inspiration here.
there. everywhere. so...
I haven't settled
on my vision just yet.
but I do see me in the center
in a fabulous display.
Where are you going to get
your costumes. props.
lighting. fog machines?
You know. there isn't much time.
My brain.
I don't have the space to think
of all the nuts and bolts.
To realize the horror and gore
deserving of our community.
I'll need help.
-Ah. Ah!
-Anyone?
I'd love to.
-You? You. too?
-Yeah.
-Oh. every... Oh. great.
Fine. I'll help.
I'm very busy.
but I live next door.
and my event is locked in.
Well. you're the best
of the best.
Thank you. Sharon.
You're welcome.
Great.
I'm gonna be so excited.
Do you know what I'm thinking.
is some found objects.
-Yeah.
-And material.
like. from the neighborhood.
Congratulations.
You're halfway there.
Collect your candy.
The maze is closing
for the costume contest.
Hurry. or the Headless Horseman
will catch you.
Boo!
Mom.
You do this every year.
Because Jump-Scare-Crow works
every year.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey. where's your costume?
Um...
See? Are you happy?
Purr-fectly.
-Mm-hmm.
-Okay. Go have fun. Be safe.
Sharon?
Good morning.
Hi. Can I help you?
I'm good.
Classic Beryl.
After a wild night.
she usually isn't awake
or home until later.
Uh. well. we're just here
to clean up the maze props.
We've got a schedule.
Oh. Go ahead.
I hereby grant you permission
as president of the
Neighborhood Events Committee.
A signature would do better.
You got it.
Happy Halloween.
Why do we have an extra head?
Oh. my God.
You're a genius.
Not my design. but I'll take it.
Hey. Rivers. check this out.
If you hold down the space bar.
you can move your cursor
wherever you want.
How did I not know that?
You know.
I'll be impressed with IT
when you guys upgrade our Wi-Fi.
IT?
Desk duty wouldn't be
half as bad
if our Internet wasn't
Stone Age dial-up.
Well. you know. in IT. we say
that patience is a virtue.
It builds character.
Something someone on desk duty
may need.
ELSBETH [Cockney accent]:
Out of my way. love.
Out of my way.
I love it.
Hey. Julia.
To what do we owe the honor?
You know. just here
-helping the old man.
-Hi. hon.
-Right on time.
-Hi. Daddy. And you're not.
Head into my office.
I'll be in there in a second.
Oh.
ELSBETH [Cockney accent]:
Not without these.
Thank you. Eliza.
We got a call.
It's a case outside the city.
They found a...
Halloween is over.
What's going on?
Cap'n. 'alloween ain't
just one day.
In here. it is.
Okay. the truth is
my costumes arrived late.
But how do you pick just one
My Fair Ladycostume?
You can't.
so I'm doing Halloweek.
I thought you were from Newsies.
Either way.
you're gonna love this.
They found a severed head.
Oh!
Whoa. cool.
But you're never gonna
guess where.
Great Neck?
I thought we picked up
all of our props.
We just kind of scoop
and then sort 'em later
-at our warehouse in the city.
-Mm.
Well. with the owner dead.
who let you in
to do all the scooping?
-Who's in charge here?
-Ugh.
Her.
Now. if you'll excuse me.
these nice suburban ladies
freak me out.
Where is Sheriff Pete?
Why is the NYPD here?
We are all terrified.
Well. I'm Detective Donnelly.
and this is Elsa?
SHARON and ELSBETH: Eliza.
Thank you.
But really. Elsbeth Tascioni.
And you are?
Sharon Norman. I live next door.
and I am president of the
Neighborhood Safety Committee.
so I demand to know.
what is going on here?
Well. we found a body
in Manhattan.
which is why we're. uh.
covering the case.
And that body appears
to have come from this maze.
Beryl Nix.
Not Beryl.
I knew that she should not
have hired those outsiders.
Who are those men?
Uh. well. he goes by Chop.
Enough said.
He said it's because
he likes chopped salad.
Do you know how Beryl died?
Because you didn't even ask
before going straight
to blaming Chop.
Well. it is simple math.
Somebody died
with people like that around?
I was not raised to be nosy.
but I-I have to know...
what happened?
We found her head.
then her body.
-Oh...
-How long have you been neighbors?
Heavens. Uh...
Let's see. It's. uh...
it's hard to think.
Uh...
She moved in. um...
...May 3. 2022.
Were you friends?
You close or...
No. but we were neighborly.
And let's just say she had
a different lifestyle.
but I respected her
and she respected...
I'm so sorry.
I'm just on edge. and...
this is very. very scary.
I have to alert the neighborhood
that there is
a killer on the loose.
Can you believe it?
Someone beheaded
in Sleepy Hollow?
Abso-bloomin'-lutely.
All right. Dad. so. once again.
we're going up here and...
I-I-I got it.
Okay. Let's see.
What the...
-I did everything right.
-Because you went to print.
but you have to choose
"Save as PDF."
Well. how does that make
any sense?
Come in.
Captain. I have an update
on the. um...
I'm sorry. I can come back if...
No. Uh. I welcome
the interruption.
This is my daughter. Julia.
Julia. Cameron.
He's one of our MEs.
-Hi.
Uh. you were saying?
Yes. So. um. we established
Beryl Nix's exact time of death
from her wrist fitness tracker's
heart rate monitor.
Exact? Uh. that's helpful.
The PPG tech
with optical heart rate sensors
used in fitness trackers
is pretty accurate.
Certainly makes my job
a lot easier.
Do you have one?
No. I'm a software engineer
who avoids exercise
if at all possible.
She's here to help
her old man with. uh.
some tech issues.
I'm the most patient
of all his kids.
I don't like the way
the IT guys here talk to me.
like I don't know
what I'm doing.
No. I-I get it. Um...
I've been trying to update
my department's software.
but. I mean. I'm afraid to ask.
And I don't even know
where to start.
I can help.
If you're looking
for a better CMS.
there's some good COTS options.
Right.
How about this? Uh...
Let's grab lunch today.
Uh. we're having lunch.
Right.
Well. how about coffee
before work
-day after tomorrow?
-Great. Yes.
I will brush up
on my acronyms before then.
Here's my number.
Just text me.
Here you go.
Will do. Thanks. Julia.
Mm-hmm.
Captain.
What?
Come on. Back to it.
Captain Luddite.
Come on.
Thank you so much
for letting me talk to you.
Everyone says
you're "the person who'd know"
when it comes
to the neighborhood.
I do like to stay connected.
Your yard is...
oh so loverly.
Thank you. I have won
Green Thumb of the Year
six years running.
Congratulations.
My grandmother
had a green thumb.
She adored violets.
I'm more of a "sell-uh"
than a "grow-uh."
Well. it relaxes me. Which is...
...what I need
at a time like this.
Have those maze roustabouts
been arrested yet?
"Roustabouts"?
You are really convinced
it was them.
Well. all I know is that.
one day. our community is safe
and. the next day.
there is a loose head.
And the only thing
that changed was them.
So. the sooner you arrest them.
the sooner
we will be safe again.
Well. Chop and his crew were
on break when Beryl died.
Getting high. no doubt.
On cheese.
They were sharing the cutest
little Halloween-themed
charcuterie board
on their truck.
One of the workers
is in culinary school.
It had these little olive...
eyeballs.
Little teeth.
Anyway.
we are looking local now.
Where were you on Halloween?
Wow. those wind chimes
carry. huh?
I don't even notice.
Um. if you need to know.
on Halloween. I was doing
my customary Jump-Scare-Crow.
Which everybody loves.
I. uh. sit on my front porch.
and then when kids come
to trick-or-treat. I jump!
And scare them.
See? I got you.
So you can ask any of the kids
who were brave enough
to visit my porch.
Oh. Right.
Uh. speaking of your porch.
I noticed the plaque.
"Towering Maple."
Was that the maple?
Your home's namesake?
You must have been devastated
to lose that.
It's nature.
It sucks sometimes.
You know.
things just come and go
and live and die. but...
...our house will
remain Towering Maple
with or without that tree.
Well. that's sweet.
Speaking of coming and going...
...as I said.
I am not one to be nosy.
but have the police talked
to any of the many men
that would visit Beryl
at all hours of the night?
Some marriages may last longer
now that she's gone.
Well. we'll definitely look
into that.
'Cause I am nosy.
Oh.
Lots of neighborhood husbands.
according to Sharon.
Yeah. lots of suspects.
according to me.
You know. Sharon knows
everything about her neighbors.
And. meanwhile.
I haven't even met one of mine.
How does that work?
Well. that's the beauty
of New York.
is everyone minds
their business.
You're only separated
by a wall or floor.
In these small towns
and suburbs.
you get more space
but less privacy.
Mm.
I suppose.
But I'd like to know who I'm
sharing walls and floors with.
I accidentally dropped one
of Gonzo's favorite toys
in the hall.
I put up notices.
and no one reached out.
Well. just because you don't
know your neighbors doesn't mean
that they're not looking out
for you.
You'll see.
That's very optimistic of you.
Must be all the Halloween candy.
No costume today?
Never mind.
Do we have any leads?
Maybe too many.
Whittle them down
and keep me posted.
Oh. uh. Cap'n?
Cap'n.
I've been trying not to ask.
but any update on Kaya?
Oh. No.
But I'm sure she's fine.
She's probably on her next case.
This is the life
of undercover work.
I understand.
I just... I miss my friend.
And I'm worried about her.
Well. I know one thing.
Kaya would love your costume.
What costume?
Who's that?
I should've known better
than to trust you.
Psycho.
I thought you were chill.
I am chill. Until I'm not.
And now I'm not.
Don't come back! Ever!
I won't!
Me and Ave would
hang at Beryl's.
We could eat. watch.
smoke what we wanted.
Our parents are uptight as hell.
-"Ave"?
-Avery.
-Avery Norman.
-Sharon Norman's daughter?
Queen Uptight herself.
Are you supposed
to be Cruella de Vil?
-Oh. Come on.
-We have
footage of you running
from Beryl's
and her chasing after you
and yelling.
You're the only person
that left Beryl's unhappy.
Lovers' quarrel?
Dude. No.
She caught me taking
her pain pills.
She had so many.
I didn't think she'd notice.
But she did.
and you saw what happened.
We certainly did. Xander.
What do you mean?
Detective Donnelly
is under the assumption that...
whomever stole
their pain pills did make them
meet their demise.
What?
I didn't make anybody
meet their demise.
What is that accent?
If anybody. it was Ave.
She wanted to kill her.
-Why don't I believe you?
-I swear.
Look at these texts.
"Oh. God. if that bitch
calls the cops on you.
I'll kill her."
Garn...
"Save as"?
You wanted to see me?
Yes.
Close the door.
I know you can't tell me much.
but...
how's Kaya?
Correct. Um. I can't.
But as far as I know.
she's fine.
And I'm sure
she'd appreciate you asking.
Well. that's good to hear.
Out of sight
but not out of mind. right?
Because some other people
are in sight.
You know what I mean?
Sir?
There are two people
that I care about
that I don't want to see hurt...
Kaya...
...and Julia.
Sir. no. our coffee...
...it's purely professional.
I know my daughter.
That may not be true
on both ends. so...
why don't we simplify things
for everyone involved?
I understand. sir.
Sorry for any misunderstanding.
Mm.
Not at all.
We all got
Ring cameras because you said.
"More eyes. less crimes."
-And look how that worked out.
-And you found the maze crew.
-The call is coming from inside the house. Sharon.
-That's very interesting.
-Sharon.
-I mean. am I wrong? Now she has nothing to say.
-Now she has nothing to say.
-Quiet!
How dare you?
I have dedicated my life
to this neighborhood.
And it was safe.
Until now.
So what changed?
Hmm? Exactly.
I think we have all learned
a very valuable lesson.
Have the police made an arrest?
I can't say.
But I'm in close communication
with them.
and it should be soon.
Do pardon our intrusion.
Ladies.
We need to talk to Sharon alone.
Well. we're
in the middle of a meeting. so...
We're gonna need to talk
to you about some texts.
And Avery.
Avery?
I swear I was not at Beryl's
on Halloween.
-But you did write those texts?
-Well. yeah.
But I didn't mean anything.
You went to Beryl's? When?
Avery. where were you
on Halloween at 8:47 p.m.?
It's okay.
You can tell them.
You were volunteering
at the costume contest.
But I wasn't.
Avery. were you
with that Xander boy?
-I am gonna make you go upstairs right now.
-No. Oh. my God.
I was with Dad.
I hate costumes.
I don't even like Halloween.
I haven't liked it
since I was 12.
That must have been
so tough for a girl growing up
in Sleepy Hollow.
Again. where were you?
My dad and I go out to eat
on Halloween.
Excuse me.
Your father was supposedly
working late.
Do you have proof of this?
You were at Splitz's Diner?
-By the mall?
-You never let me do anything fun.
Why is the photo album
titled "MFT"?
Go ahead. It's not like
it could get any worse.
Um...
"Mom-Free Time."
It's stuff my dad and I
do together without Mom.
Sorry. Mom.
Well. the metadata on the photo
shows it was taken around
the same time that Beryl died.
But...
it is possible that. uh.
Avery could have been involved.
-with a few minutes to spare.
-Mm.
No. it's not possible.
She doesn't know the maze.
It would take too long.
Well. there's only one way
to find out.
Take me through it.
I'm gonna stay here with Avery.
I am great
at puzzles. and do you see
how long this is taking me?
There is no way
that my daughter did this.
I knew that Xander boy
was trouble.
He only got into state schools.
Oh. we actually cleared him.
Yeah. he has a shoulder injury
from lacrosse.
so he couldn't have lifted
the murder weapon.
And that would be?
Oh. Right.
Um. it was a chain saw.
Yeah. We found it
in Beryl's art studio.
-Oh. my God.
-So. Xander started stealing Beryl's pain pills
for his shoulder pain when his
doctor wouldn't prescribe more.
Unbelievable.
It just goes to show.
you have no idea what's going on
in your neighbor's house.
Yeah. Or your own.
I saw the look of pain
on your face
when you learned
about Mom-Free Time.
You think you're in control.
You think you know things.
But most things are outside
of anyone's control.
Especially as a parent.
Don't you agree?
Not at all.
That is a lazy excuse
for not being involved.
I have dedicated my life to...
Being involved?
Caring.
Now. is it left or is it right?
Hmm. Oh. wait.
So. hold on. Hold on.
The call is pausing the timer.
Salutations.
They're gonna charge her?
But she's a minor.
Avery?
They're cuffing her now?
On camera?
Wow!
You move bloody fast!
Avery?! Wh-Where is she?
Is she under arrest?
Avery?
Oh. You mean the call?
Oh. no. no. no. no.
Detective Donnelly and I
were catching up
on my favorite reality show
Lavish Ladies.
Oh. the drama never ends.
No. Avery's fine.
Oh. thank God.
Oh.
Oh. thank God. Let me just catch
my breath and we'll...
resume the maze.
Uh. no. Not necessary.
I got what I needed.
You navigated your way
in and out of that maze.
no problem.
So this was a test?
-Of course.
-Of what?
My mama bear adrenaline?
Is that all?
You helped Beryl
organize that maze.
No doubt.
you had a copy of the plans.
You know every square inch
of that maze.
You big-city cops
are unbelievable.
I'm not a cop.
I'm a lady.
You come to our town
and you accuse one
of our innocent high school boys
and then you accuse
my innocent daughter
and then you accuse...
me.
The one person
that cares the most
about the safety
of this neighborhood.
Well. you know. why not?
Let's just throw it on Sharon.
Because everybody blames
everything on me anyway.
That's what I get for...
...for trying to help.
That's not true.
A lot of good
can come from helping.
So. help.
Show us big-city cops
how wrong we are
so we can focus elsewhere.
How can I help you if...
you don't believe me?
Well.
you said you were
on your porch all night.
Right?
So don't tell us...
show us.
It's in your control
to prove your innocence.
There's...
a Ring camera
at your house. isn't there?
Yeah.
Whatever's so funny?
Nothing.
I will get you that footage.
And you will see
that I was there.
All night.
We saw you on Sharon Norman's
Ring camera footage
looking very comfortable
with a chain saw.
Well. yeah. I hope so.
I cut down trees for a living.
Was one of those trees
Sharon's Towering Maple?
Yeah.
Why did you cut that down?
It was dead.
How did it die?
Old age? I don't know.
How did Sharon feel about it?
Feel? Fine.
Listen. I don't get into stuff
like that.
It's bad for business.
So. if you spend your days
sawing through big trees.
it wouldn't take you long at all
to saw through something
a little bit easier like...
Whoa.
What?
Did a lady really get her head
cut off?
And why are you dressed
like that?
-Is this a prank show?
-It can feel like that sometimes.
Why did you say
it was bad for business?
Look. I like dealing
with earth stuff. not people.
I don't want to get called in
for lawsuits.
I cut. I dispose.
and I don't ask questions.
What kind of questions
would there be?
A lot of trees
that suddenly die of "old age"
are on property lines.
Sorry to tell you this.
but your Towering Maple
may have been poisoned.
Poisoned?
Mm. No. Unlikely.
Weren't you ever suspicious?
It died so suddenly.
according to your tree doctor.
If Beryl poisoned the tree. then
I'm sure it was an accident.
Why are we talking about this?
Didn't my Ring cam footage
show that I was here?
I never said Beryl did it.
Well. who else
could it possibly have been?
She used chemicals in her art.
If the tree was poisoned. then
let's just say it was Beryl.
Okay. let's.
Then I forgive her.
Because there are
more important things in life.
I'm just surprised.
Because if someone poisoned
the namesake of my home. I'd...
You'd have to learn
to let things go. Eliza.
Like you said.
not everything
is in your control.
Now. if you don't mind?
Oh. [posh accent]: Of course.
I have a ball to get to anyway.
I just hope...
...the poison doesn't affect
the rest of your beautiful yard.
I appreciate your concern.
but I'm not worried.
What I am worried about is.
there's a killer on the loose.
Me. too.
But it shouldn't be much longer.
You warned Cameron off me.
didn't you?
Go on.
What are you worried about?
You're the boss. right?
Cameron has work to do.
How it affects his social life
is up to him.
I knew you would do this.
You never miss the chance
to throw your power around
-to mess with my life.
-Oh. is that so?
-Yes.
-It's your life.
But this precinct
and these people.
it's my world.
That is so classic.
You know I'm the only one
of your kids you'd do this to.
-Oh. come on.
-Be real. Dad.
If one of them came in here
and hit it off
with one of your officers.
you'd pull that officer in
and warn them off?
Huh?
Look at me
and tell me that's true.
I only...
ever want to protect you.
I'm 27.
I'm not this kid
you keep framed in your desk.
I don't need your protection.
I may one day want
your approval.
But only when I ask for it.
Got it.
You're 27.
You know everything.
Well. hotshot.
why don't you tell me why
I saved this file to my desktop
and it's not there. huh?
I can't with you.
Julia.
Damn it.
Any updates on Gonzo's toy?
Oh. No.
Not yet.
This whole case has me thinking
maybe I don't want
to know my neighbors.
Eh. Don't get cynical
like the rest of us.
Not yet.
So far.
Sharon's alibi checks out.
It's not helpful that
she's off-screen. but still.
Mm.
Isn't that convenient?
Ugh. I just know she did it.
I watched her dig up her plants
and replace the soil
the day after the murder.
My grandma used to let me
help her in the garden.
There's no reason to do all that
unless she knew
the poison from the tree
would spread.
But how did she kill Beryl?
There's the time of death.
and we haven't seen Sharon move.
-So it seems.
-One. two.
three. four.
-five.
-Just you wait.
Sharon Norman.
Just you wait.
♪ I ♪
♪ I... ♪
Do you mind?!
Oh.
I thought you didn't notice
Beryl's wind chimes.
This is starting to feel
like harassment.
And it was cute at first.
with the costumes. but...
you're doing a lot.
Even for Sleepy Hollow.
Halloween is over.
Oh. It's not over just yet.
We have one more scare.
We solved the murder!
How?
A fingerprint.
Come on. I'll show you.
In there?
I never got a chance
to go through the maze
when it was all dressed up.
So...
God.
No. this chain saw is
from Chop's crew.
Doesn't have a chain.
See?
None of their chain saws
had chains.
You assumed
that those outsider roustabouts
didn't care about safety.
But that was their top priority.
So I'll give them
a good Yelp review.
What do I care?
You thought.
with all of their chain saws.
they'd be blamed
for Beryl's death.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why would I care
who is blamed for Beryl's death?
Why. indeed.
Shall we?
Oh. Would you stop?
This...
is the murder weapon.
Beryl's chain saw.
You used this
to kill her
and then you stashed it back
in her art studio.
And then you gave Chop's crew
permission
to clean up the crime scene.
Your frame job complete.
you assumed your role
of concerned neighbor.
I am a concerned neighbor.
You hated Beryl.
Everyone knew it.
Your own daughter had to hide
that she spent time with her.
Hating your neighbor
does not make you a murderer.
Beryl was a nuisance
to this neighborhood.
Ask around. Everyone will agree.
We could not stand her.
Now. where is
this damn fingerprint?
I did ask around.
What are you all doing here?
-Hi. Sharon.
Oh. honey.
-Avery.
-Mom.
Beryl was cool.
She let me be myself.
And we loved her.
She had us trying fun new things
all the time.
What are you talking about?
She was sleeping
with all of your husbands.
She wasn't sleeping with them.
She was teaching them pottery
to surprise us.
We've all gotten ashtrays
-for our birthdays.
-And anniversary.
He could've done better.
We should have known when you
wanted to help Beryl with
something actually fun for once.
For once?
I don't deserve this.
Show me the evidence now.
We did find a fingerprint.
But it wasn't on the chain saw.
And it wasn't
the murderer's fingerprint.
Okay.
That's Tommy Forst.
-Keep watching.
-And brave little Tommy
was dared by his friends
to hold your hand.
-One. two...
-But the time stamp shows
-it was the exact moment that Beryl was murdered.
-...three. four.
-five.
-And you didn't move.
I don't scare everyone.
Tommy is a sensitive boy.
I did not want
to traumatize him.
We found
your Jump-Scare-Crow dummy
in the back of your garage.
And on its rubber glove...
Tommy's fingerprints.
Proving that you weren't on the
porch at the time of the murder.
I probably went to the bathroom
and changed out the dummy.
That's a perfectly reasonable
explanation.
But the fingerprint was
just enough to get us a warrant.
We tested the pipes
of the washing machine
where you washed the scrubs that
you wore when you killed Beryl.
And. well...
we found a little bit of Beryl.
Why didn't you just say that
from the beginning?!
I hate mazes!
Because...
it's the perfect end
to Halloweek.
And it really brought
the neighborhood together.
How could you all love Beryl?!
She was a killer!
She was my tree killer!
Actually. honey. that was me.
I-I thought
that removing the tree would end
your petty feud with Beryl.
But no matter
how perfect our life was.
you could never be happy.
You're all gonna miss me.
-You're gonna regret this.
-Oh...
I think Sleepy Hollow
will be just fine
without Sharon Norman.
Ha.
That was my last one. I promise.
I'll write up the report.
How's this?
"Trace amounts of blood
of the slain
stayed mainly in the drain."
-Needs work.
-Oh. no. it's perfect.
You deleted your cloud?
No.
I don't even know what that is.
But I knew
it would get you here.
Good ploy.
I'm sorry. kid.
I know it's a cliché.
but it's true.
It's hard...
...for parents to accept
their kids as adults.
Well. me at least.
Every day
I looked at this photo...
...on my desk...
...of my little girl.
At the girl I was raising
to be independent
and to make her own choices...
Don't take all the credit.
Mom did most of it.
Hey now.
But here in front of me...
...is that adult.
Inserting myself
as if I know best
was me being a bad dad.
I'll know better moving forward.
How did you get
this picture printed?
Uh. it wasn't easy.
let me tell you.
You could never be a bad dad.
Oh.
Oh. That's for me.
I have a dinner date.
Don't worry. It's not Cameron.
-Hey.
-Good night. Daddy.
Good night. Dad... er. um...
Captain.
-Sir. Uh. you know. I'm...
-Mm. Mm-hmm. mm-hmm.
Love you.
Oh.
Damn.
Damn. damn. damn.
Thank you!
Whoever you are.
Gonzo.
Look what I found.
Captioning sponsored by CBS
and TOYOTA.
Captioned by Media Access
Group at WGBH access.wgbh.org
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today